Hi, I am Morris.
Manulife Global Select MPF scheme is
targeted to onboard the EMPF platform on
November 6th this year. This means that
from this date onwards, you'll manage
your MPF and handle various MPF
administrative instructions through
EMPF. This includes switching funds,
transferring or withdrawing MPF,
consolidating personal accounts, and
more. A brand new platform means a brand
new experience. We'll share three tips
to help you transition smoothly to EMPF.
[Music]
When you receive the EMPF communication
pack sent by Manual Life, remember to
take note of the important dates listed,
including the EMPF onboarding date, the
registration start date, and the cutoff
dates for submitting MPF administration
instructions.
You can register in three easy steps
using the EMPF web portal or mobile app.
Step one, verify your identity with Hong
Kong Identity Card or through the IMS
Smart mobile app. Step two, fill in your
personal details. Step three, create a
username and password to activate your
EMPF account. No matter how many MPF
accounts you have, you only need to
register once to manage all your
accounts that have been on board to EMPF
in one place.
Don't forget to log into the Manny Life
HK and Macau app to make sure your
personal information like your name,
address, contact number, and email
address is up to date to help ensure a
smooth transfer of your Manny Life MPF
account to EMPF. If you have any
questions, don't hesitate to contact
your MPF intermediary.
To get more details about EMPF and
transition arrangements, visit Manual
Life EMPF hub. You can also join the
EMPF introductory webinars. Check more,
check better.
[Music]